<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Resist Loneliness (LOG FILE feed)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/feed.xml" rel="self"></link><id>urn:uuid:0eed6876-7ee1-3989-97f7-0e23a01607d4</id><updated>2024-10-04T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name></name></author><entry><title>04/10/2024 13:05 (Garbage)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/04102024-1305-garbage/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-10-04T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:fa850a54-ed8d-3b9a-a0db-6a7ab8f83526</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/sarif_industries_by_publiccenzor_d46v4bj.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Sarif Industries&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/publiccenzor/art/Sarif-Industries-253394335" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by PublicCenzor&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I jacked into a corpo's recruitment node today. Hate their guts, but a netrunner's gotta eat. The black market's been dry lately, and I'm not ready to dive into the high-risk jobs. I ain't no all-or-nothing type – that's just cheap simstim fodder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The test was pure brainscan garbage. Aced most of it, but the final task? Record a vidclip on why I "love finance." Pathetic corp-rats. Should've flipped 'em the bird right there on cam. They're like some alien species, not even human anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next cycle, I hit up my local street doc. Got some advice on rewiring my wetware, fine-tuning those neurotransmitter dials. Today's runtime feels smoother. Here's hoping it'll give me the edge to claw my way out of this cesspool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the cycle: This world's wired wrong. No meat puppet can feel right naturally. It's not built for living, just surviving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Doctor Flake - Voices&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Doctor Flake - Voices.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>01/10/2024 10:57 (Construct)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/01102024-1057-construct/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-10-01T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:d8d67b76-4c39-30b6-bee4-444c959c3366</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/the_audience_by_luciferasi_dgq53u5-pre.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;The audience&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/luciferasi/art/The-audience-1011367085" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by Luciferasi&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The test looms on the horizon, a digital gauntlet I gotta run. Jacked into the matrix, I scored a meet with Case's construct from Neuromancer. The legendary cowboy's still got it - dropped some primo intel on cracking corpo ICE. Respect to the old guard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These emigrant types crowding my meatspace? Null value. Reached out for a assist, nothing free, and two of 'em shut me down cold. No vision, no solidarity. Just chrome-plated egos and corp-think. Fuckin' high-riders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the cycle: When the world gives you static, rely on your own wetware. Save your cred and cycles. But sometimes you need an ally to run the shadows. Cultivate your connections - they're worth more than gold in this neon jungle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Fixions - Black Racers (Mother Russia Bleeds ost)
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Fixions - Black Racers (Mother Russia Bleeds ost).mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>29/09/2024 23:12 (Puppet master)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/29092024-2312-puppet-master/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-09-29T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:71953fb9-5548-3e8e-bb13-4181cd6838cc</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/lockdown___ouro_by_kennedy_brito_kop_by_kennedybritokop_di9cdvh-pre.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;lockdown&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by kennedybritokopr&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I drift through the neon-lit datastreams, my custom-coded bots scouring the underbelly of the net for job leads. They ping my neural interface with potential gigs, and I fire back responses, occasionally setting up meets in grimy noodle bars or smoky VR lounges. Without this automation, I'd be trapped in an endless loop, trawling through corpo job boards. The economy's in the gutter, but a street samurai's gotta eat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some chrome-plated asshole with more implants than brain cells banned me from a lucrative data stream. Fuck 'em. I've got bigger fish to fry in this digital ocean.
Had to hustle hard and divert some creds to recalibrate my brain chemistry. The daily grind was wearing me down, and hitting the synthalcohol was like slapping a patch on a severed artery - when you peel it off, the blood flows even harder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the cycle: You start to realize that even your flesh and blood are just using you, another cog in their machine. At first, it stings like a faulty wire, but then comes the cold comfort. In this neon jungle, everyone's out for themselves, feeding off the scraps tossed by the puppet masters in their high-rise havens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: UNKLE - Celestial Annihilation &lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/UNKLE - Celestial Annihilation.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>24/09/2024 11:12  (Neon-soaked Entry #42: )</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/24092024-1112-neon-soaked-entry-42/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-09-24T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:54ef0e04-1a4e-31ba-a4bf-7ea1ea215524</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/netrunner_by_thecosmicdreamer_dfvnv40-pre.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Netrunner&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/thecosmicdreamer/art/Netrunner-960174144" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by TheCosmicDreamer&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Serotonin levels flatlined. Jacked out from the corpo grind, crashed hard for 72 hours straight. World turned grayscale, interest levels zeroed out. Complete disconnect.
Need to score a mental chem subscription to boost productivity, but creds are tight. Classic catch-22 in this chrome jungle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Uncovered some nasty family skeletons while riding the low. Disappointment morphed into cold indifference. Paradoxically, it's a plus. No one to miss in this neon wasteland. The worse it gets, the better off I am.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Insomnia hit like a freight train. Navigating life with factory settings is a glitch-fest, but can't afford neural patches. Yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Started emerging from my coffin-sized pod more often. The crush of bodies and the buzz of the streets, even without direct interface, acted like a crude patch. Scored some melatonin to regulate my sleep cycle. Seems to be taking the edge off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of cycle: Sometimes the human neural net throws you a lifeline. A stranger shared their experience database, matching my situation beat for beat. Raw data makes the grind bearable. In this cutthroat datasphere, freely given intel is practically a glitch in the Matrix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Aloka -- View Source
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Aloka -- View Source.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>09/09/2024 00:06 (Arm insurance)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/09092024-0006-arm-insurance/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-09-08T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:f12870ae-173c-34a7-9ed5-a1c7befb2629</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/2D2G8UpM57xsoanRZx4RpV0trWm6GMoHcE.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;xxxxxxxxx&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="#" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by xxxxxxxxxx&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The streets of Neo-Tokyo pulsed with neon as I jacked out, my newly upgraded hand implant humming with fresh chrome. The corp suits at the insurance outfit finally coughed up the creds, and I wasted no time maxing out my deck's memory. Now I can run AI directly on my rig, no need for sketchy cloud connections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My collection of AI constructs is growing, a digital menagerie of code and potential. I've culled the weak ones, leaving only the prime specimens. For now, I'm content to observe, studying their behaviors from every angle, plotting how to leverage their power.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These text-based algos are a far cry from my usual hardware hacks, but a smart runner always diversifies their toolkit. I may not be some hotshot wordsmith, but I'll find a way to bend these digital minds to my will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the cycle: Reality can trap you in loops tighter than any black ICE, with no clear exit protocol. Always keep a backup plan in your back pocket – better yet, have two. In this unforgiving sprawl, redundancy isn't just smart, it's survival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Mefjus - Continuous&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Mefjus - Continuous.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>02/09/2024 22:47 (Neon-soaked Entry #347)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/02092024-2247-neon-soaked-entry-347/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-09-02T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:db2fb8bf-55e5-3252-acd7-c6b9770af5b6</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/peak_of__boredom__by_sea_bugg_ddoih7n-pre.png' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Peak Of 'Boredom'&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/sea-bugg/art/Peak-Of-Boredom-827233187" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by Sea-Bugg&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Sup, netrunners. Last week, my neural interface went haywire. My synthliver started churning out ethanol like a rogue nanobrewery, flooding my synapses with liquid courage. The levels weren't fatal, but they flatlined at a constant buzz.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I kept grinding out gigs, but my processing speed took a major hit. One day, my wetware glitched hard. Lost all motor control and face-planted, corrupting my cyberarm in the process. Trauma Team swooped in, ran their scripts, and patched up my hardware.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But here's the kicker - I lost two cycles in my corpo-cube. The suits initiated termination protocols - no empathy in the corporate matrix. After a full revolution, I beamed them the Trauma Team's data packet. They halted the pink slip cascade but cut me off from prime gigs. It's a glitch, but that's life in the sprawl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of cycle: When everything's running smooth, you feel invincible. When the system crashes, fear tries to take root. Stay frosty, stay focused. That's how you survive in this chrome jungle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Client_03 - Morality Corruption Splice Pointer [CE044]&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Client_03 - Morality Corruption Splice Pointer [CE044].mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>14/08/2024 19:27 (Datastreams)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/14082024-1927-datastreams/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-08-14T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:76ad8641-15cd-35ee-a744-f97f170fa6c5</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/alt_cp2077.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;character Alt (CP2077)&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by xxxxxxxxxx&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jacked into the grid, I'm still grinding away for that decrepit megacorp. No upward mobility, cred's barely trickling in, and my co-workers are straight-up corpo drones. But I ain't throwing in the towel yet. Always scanning the datastreams for fresh gigs while I streamline my current grind for kicks and downtime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cobbled together a rudimentary AI bot to handle the mind-numbing weekly tasks. It's not perfect, but it's chewing through the most braindead stuff. Solid start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My biometrics are holding steady, and my serotonin's spiking for some reason. Gotta dive deeper into my neural logs and run some self-diagnostics to figure out why.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the cycle: Sometimes reality throws you a bone when you least expect it. You don't always know the source of the high, but you ride that wave and keep pushing forward to the next cycle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Flunk - Down&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Flunk - Down.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>12/08/2024 10:00 (handful of creds)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/12082024-1000-handful-of-creds/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-08-12T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:c3d2a690-aecb-3be5-bd3a-de36849967d2</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/game_off_by_zoeragez_ddvvhtm-pre.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Game Off&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/blackcloudstudios/art/In-Game-Displays-495602613" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by zoeragez&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jacked in again, surfing the datastreams. Been diving deep lately, clocking tens of hours in medieval sims and whole fictional universes teeming with digital life. Crossed paths with a few fellow runners, all of us seeking something in this neon-lit escape. Maybe it's shelter from the gritty meatspace, or just chasing that next-level rush of connection. The tech delivers it all, for a handful of creds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the cycle: It's a worn-out line, but sometimes you gotta crash hard into the bedrock before you can kick off and rocket back to the surface. Rock bottom's just a launchpad if you've got the nerve to use it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Morcheeba - Blaze Away (Lyric Video) ft. Roots Manuva&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/Morcheeba - Blaze Away (Lyric Video) ft. Roots Manuva.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>08/08/2024 18:43 (Host location)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/08082024-1843-host-location/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-08-08T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:ff951833-a846-3329-b292-868122e35feb</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/listener_by_vedmedic_dhxg3jv-pre.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Listener&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/blackcloudstudios/art/In-Game-Displays-495602613" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by VedMedic&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another system failure hit me today, forcing my implants into hibernation mode. As I jacked back into the neon-lit sprawl, I scoured the net for any fresh gigs, but came up empty. Seems like I'm still riding the same old rails to oblivion. It's been nearly two years since I relocated to this new host, all in the name of freedom. Can't complain, though. Beats the hell out of my previous digs, where things are going from bad to worse. The nets there are crashing hard, collapsing like overripe plums (whatever those are, according to my great-grandad's ancient wisdom).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the day: Change ain't gonna come knocking on its own. You gotta make it happen, but don't expect miracles overnight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Massive Attack -Bullet Boy (Vox) (Doomed wave)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Massive Attack -Bullet Boy (Vox) (Doomed wave).mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>17/07/2024 22:24 (Logs)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/17072024-2224-logs/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-07-18T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:3e839d0c-569f-3384-b475-8710b41fb1d1</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/another_girl__another_planet__01_21__by_stellasvartur_dfzyst8-pre.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Another Girl, Another Planet (01.21)&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/stellasvartur/art/Another-Girl-Another-Planet-01-21-967402844" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by StellaSvartur&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neon-tinged data streams flicker across my retinal display as I jack into the system. All vital signs nominal. The log files scroll by in a blur of encrypted text - nutrition levels holding steady, sleep cycles within acceptable parameters, play protocols engaged.
I dive deeper, sifting through the emotional subroutines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reflection processes running at 87% efficiency. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Boredom and apathy indicators flashing yellow, but still within tolerable ranges. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energy reserves at 62% - time for another hit of synth-caf to keep the edge sharp.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The loneliness algorithm pulses a dull red, but hope and desire modules are online and functional. Confidence metrics holding firm. Joy subroutines intermittently spiking. Only the regret function shows signs of instability, but nothing critical yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I constantly monitor these streams, watching for any glitch or anomaly that could spiral into chaos. So far, the system hums along as intended. Will something emerge from this constant flow of data? Or will it all dissolve into meaningless noise? Only time will tell in this neon-drenched cybernetic existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Archive - Razed To The Ground&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Archive - Razed to the ground.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>16/07/2024 10:38 (Fight for food)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/16072024-1038-fight-for-food/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-07-16T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name></name></author><id>urn:uuid:a73d3131-f079-3e40-a5af-df0310e16faf</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/cyberpunk_2077_by_seven_teenth_de637io-pre.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Cyberpunk 2077&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/seven-teenth/art/Cyberpunk-2077-856753872" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by Seven-teenth&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UN's latest scheme to combat hunger and obesity just locked down my food automat. My AI slashed my grub expenses, blocking access to several menu items. At least I won't starve or get sick, but damn if it won't be bland as hell. Welcome to the brave new world where artificial intelligence decides what goes in your gut. No more eating whatever you want - Big Brother's watching your waistline now.
Only two ways out of this nutrient prison: jack up my income or bail to the wasteland and learn to love the taste of roasted grasshoppers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sent a few test gigs out for verification. If the corps bite and my solutions pass muster, I'll be bumping my nutrition level back up in no time. Might even score a double upgrade if I'm lucky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the Day: Creds make the world go 'round. No creds? Your world stops spinning. Ha-ha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Fritz Lang - Chapelier Fou&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Chapelier Fou - Fritz Lang.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>14/07/2024 00:24 (Black Ice)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/14072024-0024-black-ice/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-07-13T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:a72db59a-27c2-37e9-a0b8-edbafbaa9375</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/Screenshot_2024-07-14_00-38-34.png' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Night City&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="#" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by rst_lnss&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I jack into the Grid, my consciousness streaming through neon-lit data corridors until I materialize in the virtual sprawl. The city's a patchwork of corporate adverts and holographic billboards, their glare reflecting off the wet streets. I drift through the crowd, faceless avatars brushing past me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a grimy alley, I stumble upon a Chinese street food joint. The air's thick with the scent of synthetic spices. I slide onto a stool at the bar, watching the patrons. Three cookie-cutter corpo-types cycle through: sit, sip, swipe, leave. Typical NPC behavior.
Then she walks in. Flaming red hair, emerald optics gleaming like polished chrome. She's different, moves with purpose. "Who are you?" I ask, not expecting a response from what should be just another script.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She turns, fixing me with that emerald gaze. "It doesn't matter," she says, voice low and smoky. She settles her tab and vanishes into the neon-soaked night. Definitely not an NPC. Tomorrow, I'll hunt for her again in this digital labyrinth. She's something... more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the day: 3.18 creds left on my chip. Synth meat and pasta from the automat again. The system's rigged to keep you grinding for rep, stuck in your cubicle-sized apartment. But there's gotta be another way. Just need to think outside the black ice...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Tryad - Empty&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Tryad - Empty.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>12/07/2024 09:51 (Training treats)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/12072024-0951-training-treats/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-07-12T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:4538a0d6-4e36-3cc2-8eb6-046c0bf5f125</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/Lorn_screeenshot.png' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;LORN - ANVIL&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CqaAs_3azSs"&gt;by Antoine Caëcke &amp; Hélène Jeudy&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I jolted awake in my cramped sleep pod, the stench of sweat and grime filling my nostrils. Depression clung to me like a second skin, but I had to power through another day in this neon-drenched hellhole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jacking into my deck, I dove into the virtual landscape of the training center, my fingers dancing across holographic interfaces as I tackled test scenarios. This was my ticket out - a chance to clear my debts and finally afford that neuromeditator pump implant I'd been eyeing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought for the Day: I couldn't shake the fear I heard in the voices of my gene donors and sibling. Their distrust, maybe even disgust, was palpable. I knew the source - they'd been plugged into the corpo feed for too long, letting that digital poison seep into their minds like an overflowing data stream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Saltillo - A Necessary End&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Saltillo - A Necessary End.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>10/07/2024 09:42 (Free Jail)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/10072024-0942-free-jail/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-07-10T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:46d4fac3-8693-35fa-bb79-8dd5b7eaf888</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/photo_150@12-04-2018_22-06-17.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;xxxxxxxxx&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="#" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by Sergey Sokhovey&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neon-soaked twilight. Third time I've jacked out of my coffin-sized apartment today. Mainlined some synthetic caffeine, burned through two packs of cancer sticks, then slunk back inside. Other routes are locked down or hold zero appeal. At least I've got the illusion of choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I'll dive into the corporate datastream for a five-day stretch. Gotta sacrifice that chunk of my life to keep the synth-food flowing and the heat on. It's just enough to survive, nothing more. Pure, unadulterated wage slavery without the PR spin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought for the Day: Am I free? In theory, sure. But this sprawling metropolis is just a gilded cage. The moment you try to step outside the lines drawn by the megacorps, you realize how tight the leash really is. Even something as simple as crossing borders becomes a pipe dream. The world's a prison, and we're all doing time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Radiohead  - Idioteque&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Radiohead - Idioteque { Official BBC [ 16_9 ] version }.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>07/07/2024 20:27 (Data base)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/07072024-2027-data-base/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-07-07T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:1413bb62-fb21-35f3-b443-5c855bd77509</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/cyberpunk_japanese_city_street_at_night_55_by_masterartist2022_dh9w6dy.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Cyberpunk Japanese City Street at Night 55&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/masterartist2022/art/Cyberpunk-Japanese-City-Street-at-Night-55-1044542806" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by masterartist2022&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I jacked into a restricted sector of my personal databanks two cycles back. Red flags everywhere, warning labels screaming "potentially unstable," and a flashing neon sign urging me to drown my sorrows in synthetic ethanol. Like a good citizen of this neon-drenched hellscape, I complied. For 48 hours, the bootleg neurochem cocktail did its work, my meat sack sprawled in a coffin-sized sleep pod while an endless stream of algorithmically generated tunes kept my synapses firing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I finally clawed my way back to consciousness, I felt factory-fresh. No surprise that my comm stayed silent – isolation's the new normal in this chrome and concrete jungle. To verify I hadn't slipped into some digital purgatory, I pinged the old lady's neural link. Still kicking, still grinding away in meatspace. Confirmation received: I'm still trapped in this reality. All according to the script.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought for the Day: There comes a point when finding a glimmer of hope in the real world means carving yourself open with the jagged, rust-coated blade of dystopian truth. The price of awareness is paid in blood and scars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Kasra &amp; Slay - City Of Rain&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Kasra &amp; Slay - City Of Rain.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>03/07/2024 23:31 (Barrel and yacht)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/03072024-2331-barrel-and-yacht/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-07-03T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:7e24f529-4522-33d4-8a1c-bdb43191351e</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/ghetto_glitch_by_ramthewifi_ddzmuxs-pre.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Ghetto Glitch&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/ramthewifi/art/Ghetto-Glitch-845913376" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by RamTheWIFI&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b style="color:blue"&gt;rst_lnlss&lt;/b&gt;: Yo, phill0, ever jacked into the notion that creds can't buy you a slice of happiness? It's like trying to download joy into your wetware - ain't happening, choomba.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b style="color:red"&gt;phill0:&lt;/b&gt; Scan that, rst_lnlss. Everything's just chrome plating for our meat dreams. Even the shiniest tech's just a tool for executing our own code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b style="color:blue"&gt;rst_lnlss&lt;/b&gt;: Frag yeah. Been thinking I need my own cubby-hole, you know? A meat-space where no slot jockey can flatline my access. Like some kinda neo-Diogenes barrel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b style="color:red"&gt;phill0:&lt;/b&gt; Ha! You'd need some serious eddies for even a rust bucket, not to mention the titanium gonads to survive in one. But I feel ya, we all need our own corner of the sprawl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b style="color:blue"&gt;rst_lnlss:&lt;/b&gt; Word. Whether it's for plotting your next big score or just jacking out with some synthcaf. But step onto the street for a microchip, and BAM! Flattened by some corpo's sky-yacht.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b style="color:red"&gt;phill0:&lt;/b&gt; That's the way the cookie crumbles in this neon jungle, omae. We're all just trying to carve out our own little piece of silicon heaven while dodging the megacorp monoliths.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b style="color:blue"&gt;rst_lnlss:&lt;/b&gt; Ain't that the glitching truth. Welcome to the future, same as it ever was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Glen Porter - I Sat Alone&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Glen Porter - I Sat Alone.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>03/07/2024 02:24 (Dali day)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/03072024-0224-dali-day/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-07-02T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:acdd4516-0b91-3547-9bb9-da854dee22b4</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/tv_girl.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;xxxxxxxxx&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/blackcloudstudios/art/In-Game-Displays-495602613" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by xxxxxxxxxx&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's been a glitched-out day for me. First, my deck got a software update that fried the video output. I know updates are a dangerous game, but I'm just cocky enough to think I can handle any problem on the fly. That's pretty much what happened. Never mind, I've made my call, I'll deal with the consequences later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During a net convo, my audio implant suddenly went dark. Shit, I thought it had plenty of juice, but it seemed dead as a disconnected drone. I cracked it open, checked the voltage, and plugged in a power cable. After two hours of tense waiting, it flickered back to life. Exhaled a sigh of relief, crisis averted.
Caught a good transmission from an underground station near midnight. Nice slice of the hidden datastream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the day: Just do it, choomba. If your energy's low, crawl through the neon-lit gutters. Sometimes it'll bring you results, other times... a fatal incident might cut your life short. C'est la vie in the sprawl. That's something to keep jacked into your wetware, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound:  Archive - Sleep&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Archive - Sleep.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>01/07/2024 08:43 (Wired connection)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/01072024-0843-wired-connection/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-07-01T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:27f9be3c-85db-3e60-b887-1b0666ef7572</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/cyberpunk__by_arsynnx_dhou4y9.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Cyberpunk &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/arsynnx/art/Cyberpunk-1069641873" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by Arsynnx&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neon-soaked weekend, jacked in non-stop. Only unplugged for quick synth-food hits. Rode the datastreams hard - coding, gaming, and buzzing the chatrooms. Good times in the electric haze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stumbled on some prime gigs in the shadows. Could be my ticket to the big leagues if I play it right. Gonna dive in, see if I can crack 'em.
Tweaked my rig's innards, boosted the connection stability. Should hold up better in the high-traffic zones now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the day: When you're waiting on something heavy, don't let it fry your circuits. Keep your mind occupied with unrelated biz. Keeps the anxiety daemons at bay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay frosty out there in the sprawl, choombas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Blockhead - Never Forget Your Token&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Never Forget Your Token.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>29/06/2024 00:25 (Coffee, break)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/29062024-0025-coffee-break/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-28T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:ff801677-9414-3748-b4d3-a44e3623b37e</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/ismail-inceoglu-well-don-t-mind-me1.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Well, don't mind me!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.artstation.com/artwork/GaDNXQ" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by Ismail Inceoglu&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neon-lit streets beckoned as I jacked out for a caffeine fix. Ten meters from my local synthbrew joint, I clocked a chrome-armed suit about to hurl something. My wetware kicked into overdrive, adrenaline surging. My Provessor implant ran threat assessment, calculating trajectories faster than meat-thought could process.
False alarm. The suit was just rage-quitting his PDA, smashing corp property like it was going out of style. Crisis averted, I ghosted past and scored my fix - black as the Net and twice as wired.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier, I'd spliced a custom hack into the corpo OS. Risky biz, but it turbocharged my workflow. Spent the whole day swimming through datastreams, tweaking code like a digital god.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back in meatspace, I'm still waiting for my first real-world programming gig. For now, it's all sim-jobs and virtual grunt work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the day: In this neon jungle, honesty's just another commodity. If you can lie without consequences, do it. Street cred comes to those who can spin a smart tale. It's the way of the world, omae. Just make sure your fabrications are as bulletproof as your firewall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Code 64 - Guardian&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Code 64 - Guardian.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>25/06/2024 22:29 (Chiba?)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/25062024-2229-chiba/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-25T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlnss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:9d579a07-847d-3130-85e5-03708a214100</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/wr731_by_aaron888_ai_dhnhhef.png' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Wr731&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/aaron888-ai/art/Wr731-1067371863" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by Aaron888-AI&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neon-tinged rain slicks the grimy streets as I jack into my deck, scrolling through the data feed from my Chiba junkyard sensor. The temp readout's been glitching, flickering in and out like a dying neon sign. After a deep dive into the hardware, I realize it's not the sensor itself - though the power units are running on fumes. Turns out some rogue code was causing the malfunction. Half an hour of furious typing later, I've squashed the bug. Now the temp should beam straight to my HUD, clear as the corporate skyline on a rare smog-free day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Ceschi - Beauty For Bosses&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Ceschi - Beauty For Bosses.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>24/06/2024 23:55 (Digital Scavenger)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/24062024-2355-digital-scavenger/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-24T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:0d573d78-20f8-3d74-8119-6e5cff170685</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/manga_by_brokenteapotstudios_dhn60zv.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Manga&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/brokenteapotstudios/art/Manga-1066837387" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by BrokenTeapotStudios&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scored a new rig today - top-of-the-line router with the latest wireless protocol. It's solid, but I still need power units. Price tag's way out of my league though.
Got a lead on a free data stream. Gotta jack in and hook up a neural net for translation. Looks like it's streaming criminal intel from my sector. Jackpot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My language implant's acting like a damn potato. Need new creds, but that gig's gonna flay my wallet raw.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Capsule admin's been riding my ass about a new OS. Wanted me to boost some corpo software without paying, but that sheet's more buggy than a roach motel. Told him to chill - I've got connections. Installed the newest Deckeres OS for free. That'll keep him quiet for a while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time to dive into the neon sea and see what treasures I can fish out with this new setup. The streets are calling, and they've got stories to tell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Archive - Pills (Version)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Archive - Pills (Version).mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>24/06/2024 01:34 (の充電 - 22分間のホログラフィックな昼寝)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/24062024-0134-22/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-23T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:af8164ce-1f04-316c-99b2-dd7805b75c5f</id><content type="html">&lt;iframe width="760" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xMkCgAoJFBk" title="Androidの充電 - 22分間のホログラフィックな昼寝 A021323(Android recharge - 22 minute holographic catnap)" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>23/06/2024 01:12 (Clean and burn)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/23062024-0112-clean-and-burn/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-22T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:70df32f6-0791-3110-954b-a002b3f3c705</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/netrunner_security_chip_by_lucasdurham_d9arg6ss.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Netrunner Security Chip&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/blackcloudstudios/art/In-Game-Displays-495602613" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by LucasDurham&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, I was mostly jacked into meatspace. Reality's got its own protocols, signals, and objects, just like the 'net, but with one crucial difference: it's all analog, an indeterminate material realm teeming with billions of wetware nodes. One of those nodes—a human—was frying their synapses, system failure, error, faulty calculations. The friendly runner who picked up my transmission diagnosed me as either drunk or glitching hard. My signal didn't get through. For now, I'm out of options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Purged the clutter from my hole. Ran a co-op session, made some serious progress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the day: If you don't grok something, log it and circle back later. Today, I finally understood why cleaning a carpet costs ten creds less the first time around. Took me a while, but I got there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Endanger - Blood Red Roses (feat. Kiara M.E)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/endanger feat. KIARA M.E. - Blood Red Roses (Official Homestyle Video).mp3
" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>21/06/2024 21:29 (NOTICE: ai_module Sonet enabled, dummy mode)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/21062024-2129-notice-ai_module-sonet-enabled-dummy-mode/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-21T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:377e5fc0-91cb-37b4-9e9d-5a470f8c4625</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/red_light_for_him_by_damage9292_dgl6rf6.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Red light for him&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/damage9292/art/Red-light-for-him-1003046226" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;By DAMAGE9292&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I jacked into the corporate grid at 0600, neural implants humming as I synced with the data streams. All day, my meat prison slumped in an ergonomic chair while my consciousness swam through seas of neon digits and holographic spreadsheets. Made countless micro-decisions, each one a spark in the vast machine of corporate profit. Executed protocols, optimized workflows, all without a single original thought. Just another cog in the megacorp machinery.
As I disconnected, the world of flesh and blood seemed dull, almost unreal. The harsh fluorescents of the office cube farm assaulted my eyes, a poor imitation of the vibrant cyberscape I'd been immersed in. My head throbbed, synapses still firing with phantom data.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Thought for the day: We're all just wetware running corporate software. The illusion of choice is the most efficient form of control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Le Peuple de I'Herbe - I'm asking&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/LE PEUPLE DE L'HERBE - I'm asking.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>20/06/2024 21:19 (Arrest the sky)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/20062024-2119-arrest-the-sky/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-20T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:4b80ae2d-9178-34b0-b82e-6e6b8c64161d</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/eutropia_by_vincentiusmatthew_deqio30-fullview.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Eutropia&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/vincentiusmatthew/art/Eutropia-891067500" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by VincentiusMatthew&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm back in my hole again and don't come out. After returning from vacation, I decided to take another vacation at my own expense, they didn’t approve, I had to deal with company affairs, here my freedom would have been to tell them to go to hell and fly out into the street, but the dice fell out in such a way that they fucked me off now I can mind my own gigs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My social battery is running low. Yesterday, one of the artists I value got snagged by the police of mind, if she were a decker, maybe she could've sliced her way out, but artists ain't wired like that, and they reject help until it’s too late, their way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought for the day: Don’t stop looking around, even if you don’t see anything unusual, today when I went out to get coffee I was stunned by the sky after the rain, I’m still bruised.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: :Wampscut: - Muselmann (2011 - Remaster 2017)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/30. Muselmann (2011 - Remaster 2017).mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>19/06/2024 08:31 (Troitsky Option)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/19062024-0831-troitsky-option/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-19T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:f5838beb-da2d-3259-9b95-3e321791d693</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/shadowrunner_atomic_sankara_by_thanhool_dh13tbs.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Shadowrunner Atomic Sankara&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/thanhool/art/Shadowrunner-Atomic-Sankara-1029782584" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by thanhool&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neon Morning, Friends and My Best Friend I.
The vacation ended, and I once again plunged into the abyss of social interactions to earn those few credits that keep me from being thrown out onto the neon streets of this anthill, joining the junk beggars and petty thieves. The first days showed that my vacation was very productive. I've adjusted my patterns, calibrated my reactions, and now I feel much better in the storm of emotions swirling around me, simply because I have my own boundaries and point of view. Good.
The only project I worked on during my vacation was a prototype of a fortune-telling machine. From hundreds of gigabytes of books in different languages, it can generate a pseudo-random quote, which will be the result of the fortune-telling - a seed that might push my brain off the ground, or maybe not. In any case, it won't make things worse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's my fortune for today:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;&amp;quot;Obviously, identifying an article that will be significant is very difficult.&amp;quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Newspaper Troitsky Option # 45 (19_01_2010)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/08062024-2214-location-log-entry/"&gt;Location entry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Alphawezen - Electricity Drive&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Alphawezen - Electricity Drive.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>16/06/2024 21:08 (Optical illusion)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/16062024-2108-optical-illusion/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-16T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:5f9c14c2-c90d-3e65-821a-e1b20b1897c6</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/cyberbunk_coffee_shop_live_wallpaper_by_nightcoregang_ddro2xz.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Cyberbunk Coffee Shop&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/nightcoregang/art/Cyberbunk-Coffee-Shop-Live-Wallpaper-832533479" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by NightcoreGang&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I went out to the store for energy drinks and coffee. On the way, I looked at the clouds that crowded in the sky after a thunderstorm; the warm summer wind pleasantly blew across my face and hands. I went to the coffee machine and began to choose my usual strong coffee. The machine screen flickered and instead of the standard menu with the amount of loaded credits, I saw: World v 0.1 b. As soon as I tried to comprehend what I saw, I blinked and the next moment I already saw the usual menu. The optical implants are glitching, we need to run diagnostics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Unkle - Be There (feat Ian Brown)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Unkle - Be There (feat Ian Brown).mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>16/06/2024 01:45 (Black-white lines)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/16062024-0145-black-white-lines/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-15T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:fe488be1-c809-3c84-8613-8aed1bf349ca</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/IW.jpg' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;IDEALIZED WORKSPACE&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.daveyperkins.com/" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by Devey Perkins&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neon-lit night, two cycles left before the end of my neuro-break. A tinge of melancholy seeps through my circuits. In this dystopian megacity, we toil endlessly for sustenance and shelter. You can take off your pants and don't owe anyone, but this won’t last long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meatspace adventures: riding the giga-wheel, exchanging data with a fellow street-runner, and acquiring neural-link audio enhancers. The enhancers are black-market clones, thrice as cheap as the corp-sanctioned originals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Co-op mission: progress achieved, synergy established.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A full cycle immersed in the Matrix, assimilating fresh intel and subroutines. Rapid neural adaptation, objectives accomplished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data-stream of the cycle: In the sprawling urban labyrinth, cycles oscillate between the tolerable and the insufferable. A cliché, but an undeniable truth etched into the very fabric of our existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Ashbury Heights - Kingdom Confession&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Kingdom Confession.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>14/06/2024 18:42 (01. Sound line release aka SLR)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/14062024-1842-01-sound-line-release-aka-slr/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-14T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:a01e0e5c-e143-3a84-b258-dd56e8f288d9</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;What is this?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/enter____by_dark_indigo_dby94ag-fullview.jpg' &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Enter...&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/dark-indigo/art/Enter-722660344" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by Dark-Indigo&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greetings, fellow netizen. If you've managed to decrypt this transmission, then there's still hope in this neon-drenched dystopia we call reality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You've stumbled upon a clandestine data package, a monthly supplement to my half-fiction log file, "Resist Loneliness." It's a collection of audio and visual fragments I've salvaged from the depths of the sprawling digital landscape.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consider this a manifesto of sorts:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I initiated this underground data stream out of sheer frustration with the mind-numbing content and the soulless drones I once called companions. I severed all ties with the thematic channels and chatrooms, rejecting the endless stream of vapid video feeds. In the precious time I reclaimed, I delved deep into the network's hidden layers, unleashing my imagination upon the glitching ruins of our world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Within this encrypted archive, you'll uncover a pirated collection of music, each track linked to a specific log entry. These sonic artifacts somehow resonated with me, though I've attached no additional semantic burdens to their digital essence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The data package also contains an array of images, fragments of my log's visual narrative. The choice of how to utilize them falls upon you, but tread carefully—many are the intellectual property of others. Respect the work of your fellow creators in this unforgiving digital realm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this transmission brings a flicker of light to your existence, then my mission has found its purpose. Stay strong in your search for meaning amidst the chaos, and may fortune favor your journey through the neon-lit shadows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thaks for support,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Regards, Resist Loneliness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inspired: rekt.network&lt;br&gt;
Feedback: resist-loneliness@blooddrop.live&lt;br&gt;
Password: glitch&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;01-RL-SOUND-LINE-Jun-14.zip&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
    &lt;a href='/static/sound_line_archives/01-RL-SOUND-LINE-Jun-14.zip'&gt;Download⇓&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>14/06/2024 00:13 (Fail and bar)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/14062024-0013-fail-and-bar/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-13T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:c17767b9-4746-35cd-b2c4-72d0844a1fb1</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/lively_p.gif'&gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Breath&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/rocksdanister/art/Breath-827566499" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by rocksdanister&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another cycle in the sprawl, and my tech's taken a hit. My top-of-the-line auditory enhancers are glitching out, one side dead as a fried circuit. No fix-it joints within a megaclick radius, but I've got a backup pair stashed, so it's not a total loss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mused on it earlier, plugged into a meetup on graphical neural nets. Thought it might spark something, but it was a dud. Starting to feel like this whole city's a ghost town when it comes to finding anyone on my wavelength.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the day: Makes me wonder when I started expecting so much from the meatbags around me that reality keeps coming up short. Do I keep lowering the bar till there's nothing left? What's that leave me with - something I can still call human? And what about the others out there, the ones I've heard whispers of, operating on a level so far beyond my own it might as well be another universe?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Gasoline - Getto Anthem&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Getto anthem (feat. Aerodrink).mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>12/06/2024 22:13 (Music and backup)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/12062024-2213-music-and-backup/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-12T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:309b1bd7-bf6c-3fe9-bf07-927dc04420b3</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/a_call_for_you_by_ossdesign_d6jep3i.jpg' &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;A call for you&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/ossdesign/art/A-call-for-you-395395470" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by ossdesign&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I jolted awake, my neural implants syncing with the grid. A quick scan of my surroundings revealed nothing out of the ordinary. The neon glow of the city seeped through the cracks in the blinds, but the silence was deafening. I drifted back into a dreamless sleep, only to be roused hours later by the incessant pinging of my biometric monitors. The readouts confirmed I was still alive, my vitals stable. I stumbled out of bed, desperate for a hit of synthcaf to kickstart my system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pulsing beat of electronic music was the only thing that could penetrate the fog of my mind. Thoughts of venturing out into the gritty streets flickered and died, crumbling to pixels in the face of apathy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As night fell, the power grid faltered, plunging the city into darkness. My backup generators hummed to life, keeping my critical systems online. But some subroutines failed to initialize, forcing me to dive into the tangled web of code to troubleshoot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the day: I think we have reached a technological singularity, but we don’t understand it, new chips and technologies are appearing, but forums and news are shouting that we have no idea how to use it, let’s buy it, and then think for yourself why you need it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Ghinzu - Turn Up the Satan&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/turn_up_the_satan.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ta0ma0.github.io/rst_lnlss_blog/blog/08062024-2214-location-log-entry/"&gt;Location entry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content></entry><entry><title>11/06/2024 23:11 (Journey and threads)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/11062024-2311-jorney-and-threads/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-11T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:c29947c3-7520-364e-b836-fda313da1e76</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/neural_gibson.jpg' class=leftimg&gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Author&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="#" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by rst_lnlss (AI)&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I boot up from sleep mode, my neural implants quickly process the remnants of a dream, a simple simulation that almost perfectly mirrored my current situation. Strange, my subconscious is usually more efficient than this, never lagging behind reality. A first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I sync my wireless Audiotechnica headphones and queue up an old audiobook as I set up a backup virtual machine in the cloud. They need me to establish a secure connection from any PDA on the globe to a private network, a gig that still pays the bills. Just a precaution to avoid future complications, though I doubt I'll need it. But it brings a certain tranquility, and I need to keep my circuits occupied somehow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For 90% of the cycle, I was immersed in a virtual realm conceived by a brilliant mind nearly three decades ago, a world that resonated with my very code. I witnessed something that existed only within the creator's imagination, an utterly illusory construct that nonetheless wove its threads through countless networks, spawning hundreds, perhaps thousands of derivative visions, undoubtedly altering the lives of many - for the better, I firmly believe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the day: Through his protagonist, this visionary scribe asserted that to journey somewhere, one must possess the desire to arrive. Sound advice for the masses, spoiled for choice among the myriad models of happiness peddled by designers and executives. But I must persist in my own quest, for I perceive with stark clarity that the happiness on offer is hastily manufactured, a mere facsimile of the genuine article.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Juno Reactor - Mona Lisa Overdrive&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Mona Lisa Overdrive.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ta0ma0.github.io/rst_lnlss_blog/blog/08062024-2214-location-log-entry/"&gt;Location entry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content></entry><entry><title>10/06/2024 22:18 (WARNING: Low motivation level)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/10062024-2218-warning-low-motivation-level/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-10T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:03902fe5-0041-3b46-b20f-0bc3471a6a4a</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/in_game_displays_by_blackcloudstudios_d872hf9.png'&gt;

  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;In-Game Displays&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/blackcloudstudios/art/In-Game-Displays-495602613" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by blackcloudstudios&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morning. I opened my eyes and glanced at my neurotransmitter levels and to-do list. Next to each item, a red "insufficient motivation" warning icon flashed. I closed my eyes again and fell into an even deeper, dreamless sleep. Waking up late in the afternoon, I was convinced that the levels hadn't changed, but I pulled myself out of bed anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I turned on the emergency power supply and brewed coffee from my emergency stash, lacking the strength to venture to the machine on the street. The servos began to hum, and I mustered the energy to perform daily maintenance and cleaning. Time to move on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before leaving my apartment, I always check for an agent's car parked outside my window. Before opening the door, I scan the space in front of it—my usual ritual. They might still be hunting me, even though the sensors have been silent for a long time. In this world, vigilance is a constant necessity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The machine-made coffee restarted my internal mechanisms, and I'm alive again. I need to deal with this. A request to the AI provided me with the following list:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dopamine
Serotonin
Norepinephrine
Oxytocin
Endorphins
Cortisol&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The problem lies here. I messaged my chemist; we'll see how many credits it will cost me and figure out the next steps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought for the day: Even when you don't have enough energy for anything, there's always some minimal action you can take. You need to think and do it. Maybe this small step will lead to a more level playing field, as it did for me today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Neouroticfish - Depends on You&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Depend On You.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ta0ma0.github.io/rst_lnlss_blog/blog/08062024-2214-location-log-entry/"&gt;Location entry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content></entry><entry><title>09/06/2024 23:12 (Shot in the sky)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/09062024-2312-shot-in-the-sky/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-09T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:29668385-881e-3f24-b6ad-68ebec9955ad</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/the_red_onna_musha___xi_by_sinakasra_dexi36s.jpg'&gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;THE RED ONNA-MUSHA - XI&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/sinakasra/art/THE-RED-ONNA-MUSHA-XI-902797732" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by sinakasra&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The neon lights pierce the night sky like a shot, injecting with a dose of electric brilliance. My neural implants finally grant me a moment. I drag myself out of bed, slip on my shades, and stumble towards the coffee machine. The morning caffeine hit surges through my veins, a welcome jolt to my system. The faint scent of gasoline lingers in the kitchen-turned-workshop, a remnant of yesterday's Zippo repair session.
I need to compile the documentation files after configuring the ZNC bouncer, ensuring that next time I won't have to scour the net for instructions. It's a simple task, but the documentation keeps me occupied, focused.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, the runners and I tackled a co-op mission, making significant progress. Our shared triumph is a source of encouragement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rest of the day is spent pondering new projects, creating backups, and grappling with the nagging suspicion that something crucial is missing, hindering my progress. The exact nature of this obstacle eludes me, for now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond the window, the world ceases to exist. I pay it no mind, as it neither bothers nor interferes with my existence. It's perfect, in its own way. My online village, a digital commune where everyone shares everything—mostly memes and good vibes—is all I need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the day: We overestimate our influence on those closest to us. In reality, no one truly influences anyone. If your friend descends into madness, you are powerless to help them. We are too self-absorbed, too distrustful of others to make a real difference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Polybius  - Eat Them All&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
   &lt;source src="/static/sound/02. Eat Them All.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>08/06/2024 22:14 (Location log entry)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/08062024-2214-location-log-entry/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-08T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:96e15547-64ad-3664-9208-fe3ab04a7174</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/medai_god.jpg' class=leftimg&gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;God Media&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="#" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by rst_lnlss (AI)&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm on Earth in the Mountains, a country connected to the global data highway. But in the net-sector, it's just a pixel, nothing seeming important. All the better for me - less regulations, almost free. In the sector I relocated from, the net lost connectivity. That's not acceptable for me. I know how to bypass walls and firewalls, but I prefer to walk freely, to breathe, to inhale free bytes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are fewer augmented people here than anywhere else. People prefer clean bodies, and this is good. The thoughtless use of implants is spreading epidemics of cyberpsychosis and increasing the number of unpredictable glitches. I'm running towards reasonable predictability.
Access to the network doesn't become faster or more brilliant if you do it from a 500-level skyscraper. The same access can be had from a building built from natural tuff, a material used here even before the invention of the first stone highways for wheeled transport.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Access to chips and hardware is somewhat slower, but the space is saturated with a large number of earlier hardware models at an affordable price, which is quite enough for my activities. And if you need the latest sparkling chrome, then a proxy is at your service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's important to note the low level of police corruption and their good equipment. This ensures that there are no unwanted problems from unexpected quarters. To get these problems, you need to try very hard or behave completely crazy. It's good, good. No one bothers you here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: NEUS - Downrising&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/NEUS - Downrising.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ta0ma0.github.io/rst_lnlss_blog/blog/08062024-2214-location-log-entry/"&gt;Location entry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content></entry><entry><title>08/06/2024 04:25 (Pazzles and trifle)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/08062024-0425-pazzles-and-trifle/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-07T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:b196cd61-b85b-36f5-af2a-6cbd37694fd3</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/vr_girl.jpg' class=leftimg&gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;VR&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="#" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by rst_lnlss&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the neon-drenched morning, I ventured to the post office to retrieve a package containing my single board computer. The city's pulse thrummed through the streets, a symphony of data streams and electric dreams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upon powering up the rig, it failed to materialize in my net. A challenge, indeed, but one I relished. After all, it's why I sought them out—to sink my teeth into the problems they presented. I ran through the usual diagnostics: checking the path cord, resetting the router. No dice. Time to start from scratch.
I slotted in a fresh SD, rolled out a new OS, tweaked the settings. Viola! The rig hummed to life, its circuits singing in perfect harmony. A twinge of disappointment flickered through me; with the issue resolved, I found myself without a puzzle to unravel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My mind's eye wandered over my hardware array, assessing its capabilities, yearning for a project to sink into. But what I lacked was a clear-cut task, a problem with a specific endgame and, of course, a surefire payoff. Without that, my brain refused to engage. It's a tale as old as Edison himself—one invention every seven years. My case was far from unique in this neon-soaked world.
A thought flickered through my mind, a glimmer of insight amidst the city's digital haze: If you leave your change behind in one coffee machine, let your worries drift away on the data streams. In fifteen minutes, you'll find it waiting for you in another, a small treasure in this labyrinthine metropolis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound:  :Wumpscut: My Leper Kid&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/01. My Leper Kid.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ta0ma0.github.io/rst_lnlss_blog/blog/08062024-2214-location-log-entry/"&gt;Location entry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content></entry><entry><title>06/06/2024 23:51 (Approximate approach)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/06062024-2351-approximate-approach/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-06T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:6041ae4d-8945-3ba9-bdde-600ecb7a3699</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/holy_war_by_adam_varga_d8uilkd-pre.jpg'&gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Holy War&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/adam-varga/art/Holy-War-534985645" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by Adam-Varga&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neon mornings with earbuds on, jacking into my favorite brunch spot. I grab a quick hit of oxytocin from my runners and a shot of spirits to wake up the grown-up in me. I may not have an experienced medical chemist on call, but I try to maintain the balance of my neurotransmitters by any means available. Friendly communication is fine, but sometimes it's a burden, both for me and others. That's just how people function in this world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decide to grab breakfast at the most likely cafe, run by double emigrants who've made a full cycle of resettlement, fleeing from the eternal war of dictators. The food is delicious, and the owner throws in a small gift of ice cream. Good stuff.
My approach to life is controlled chaos. I calculate the probability and call my driver, requesting a route to one of the ancient churches. Gotcha. We drive along the road to our destination, passing ancient rocks and ruins. I take a moment to drink cold, natural water from what's probably a sacred source, going off-grid to think without thinking. Finally, we return safely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A quick check of my deck's RAM shows everything is in order. I browse the runners' forum for project examples that might lead to my next gig.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thought of the day: We can't calculate everything. Sometimes, we have to make decisions using heuristic algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Mari Kattman - Night Life&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/02 Night Life.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ta0ma0.github.io/rst_lnlss_blog/blog/08062024-2214-location-log-entry/"&gt;Location entry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content></entry><entry><title>05/06/2024 17:06 (Room &amp; Akira)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/05062024-1706-room-and-akira/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-05T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:1ca2ca73-0f1d-3808-9f47-be43fc5d1b14</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/akira-hed-2020.jpg'&gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Akira&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0094625/?ref_=fn_al_tt_1" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by Katsuhiro Ôtomo&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm jacked into my rig, immersed in the neon-soaked beats of the music world. No need to venture out into the gritty streets. A few small gigs keep me from flatlinning, but I need more, always scanning for contracts. The job market's a fraggin' mess, too many desperate souls and not enough work to go around. Freelancing? Gotta update my profile and keep a closer eye on the net, but I ain't got the drive for that yet. My mind's always buzzing, searchin' for the next big score, a project to call my own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today's my birthday, but ain't no reason to celebrate. Might link up with some fellow runners for a quick meet. Scored a sushi set called Akira, named after that legendary anime. Heh, the irony.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A runner once told me: Don't leave the room, don't make a mistake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Thylacine - Home&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/THYLACINE - Home.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ta0ma0.github.io/rst_lnlss_blog/blog/08062024-2214-location-log-entry/"&gt;Location entry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content></entry><entry><title>03/06/2024 22:49 (Zippo Fuel Crisis)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/03062024-2249-zippo-fuel-crisis/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-03T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:8a3b19f2-2b29-39c2-aecb-95eba25fd3c2</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/fuel_stop_by_jacobcharlesdietz_d7z42d1-fullview.jpg'&gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Fuel Stop&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/jacobcharlesdietz/art/Fuel-Stop-482239477" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by JacobCharlesDietz&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zippo Fuel Crisis
Got a Zippo lighter, but no Zippo fuel. Tried 97% alcohol, solvent, nothing worked. Might need to hit the gas station. I'll give it a shot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ATM Malfunction
Morning update: ATM card's busted. Gotta grab cash from the office. Time to renew the card? At least prices aren't surging. NFC to the rescue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Video Stream Conversion
Found a slick program for real-time video stream conversion. Snag a source, layer on effects, route it to another output and beam it across the Net. Feels like Linux.
Birthday Bash&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Birthday party time. My old friend's gone off the grid. Probably couldn't find the right meds. New faces from some corner of the Net showed up instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AI Access Request
In a restricted sector with no free AI access, they're asking for a way in. Gotta ponder that one.&lt;/p&gt;
</content></entry><entry><title>02/06/2024 22:25 (Wavy headphones)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/02062024-2225-wavy-headphones/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-02T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:665ecf6c-98ba-36e5-b1e3-4562ebc5ef48</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/neon_cityscape_by_xtremetoxicguy_daele89.png'&gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Neon Cityscape&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/xtremetoxicguy/art/Neon-Cityscape-629174601" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by xtremetoxicguy&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this neon-drenched hellhole of a town, there ain't a single chips and micro-electronics store to be found. All I need is a simple 3.5 jack connector for my headphones, but I'm stuck soldering this piece of junk together with scrap metal and duct tape. Four hours of my life, gone. I might have to jack into the capital's grid and see what I can scrounge up, but that's a problem for another day. Got a few backup plans up my sleeve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Linked up with some runners in the chat, setting up a Jitsi for a virtual meet. Ran into some dependency issues, but I'm a quick thinker. Found a workaround and got it installed. I'm wired in now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jacked into a co-op game for a couple of hours. We tore through the forest, leaving a trail of pixelated animal carcasses in our wake. Racked up the points until the spawn rate couldn't keep up. Saved our progress and jacked out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today's truth: In this fast-paced, neon-lit world, planning years ahead is a fool's game. Life's got a way of jamming your circuits and frying your plans. Best to strap on your headphones, crank up the tunes, and ride the wave wherever it takes you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Beborn Beton - My Monstrosity (Sydney Vallette Remix)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/15. My Monstrosity (Sydney Valette Remix).mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>02/06/2024 02:50 (Battery it is Energy)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/02062024-0250/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-06-01T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:c0770e4b-f7a4-3818-a1a3-b4ad673ae84a</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/addict.jpg' class=leftimg&gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Addict&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="#" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;None&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neon-lit morning. Jacked into the grid, I navigate the sprawl to the electronic bazaar. Mission: score an SD-card for my PDA and accumulators for a DIY power bank kit. Gotta stay juiced and connected out here. Transfer complete. Load up my favorite synth-wave tracks onto the PDA for untethered audio bliss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow need repair my headphones, music it's my air, I'm is audio junke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jack into the net for some co-op gaming with a couple of rogue runners I linked up with in the dark alleys of cyberspace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time ticks on, each moment a digital drop in the ocean of existence. Boring or thrilling, it's all just data streaming by, an endless flow of binary indifference in the neon-drenched landscape of the sprawl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Cinephile - Comatose&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Cinephile - Comatose.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>31/05/2024 22:52 (PDA and zombies)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/31052024-2252-pda-and-zombies/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-05-31T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:2e7f3272-bd87-3b1c-9919-380127f6167a</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/hexaphone_660_by_duskie_06_degp8t2-pre.png'&gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Hexaphone 660&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/duskie-06/art/Hexaphone-660-874578134" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by Duskie-06&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The neon glow of the city seeped through the cracks of my blinds as I jolted awake, my neural implant buzzing before the caffeine hit my system. The holographic display of my phone flashed, revealing the face of my apartment's AI administrator demanding the monthly payment. I stumbled to the ATM, only to find my cred-chip malfunctioning. Forced to withdraw physical cash from the office, I made my way to the electronic store, driven by an inexplicable urge to acquire a mini-computer running Android OS. Despite my preference for Linux, the allure of Android's sleek interface proved irresistible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upon returning home, reality struck me like a glitch in the matrix—today was Friday, a working day, not the liberation of Saturday I had initially believed. A bittersweet realization washed over me; while the corporate machine had not yet fully consumed my mind, its grasp on my life was undeniable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The revelation of the day hit me like a rogue lines of code: Social programming is not just a theory, but a tangible force shaping the very fabric of our society. I witnessed firsthand how those exposed to its influence transformed, their thoughts and actions molded by the invisible strings of the system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Felio - Rituals Tape •67&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;iframe width="300" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-TuFg1iqTns" title="Felio - Rituals Tape •67" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>31/05/2024 00:27 (Blood and bot)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/31052024-0027-blood-and-bot/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-05-30T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:bc537b85-1c6c-37d4-bfbe-be414af1fdf7</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='/static/corban_dallas_taxi.jpg'&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This morning, I hadn't yet charged up on caffeine when my smartphone buzzed. It was a call from the blood bank; they asked me to donate blood today. Alright, I'll gather my strength for tomorrow. I tapped the holographic map to call a taxi. It was a known driver, Trooper. All the way, he repeated propaganda takes—I'd already tried to tune it out, just another bot. After arriving at the bank, another driver with upgraded brain chips picked me up. We laughed all the way; it was good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Near home, I went to the drug store for iron-containing supplements to restore my blood, but it was closed due to problems with documents. No worries, I'll just head to the nearest one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wrote a little in the dead cyberpunk chat. Why call it dead? People are just depressed and jaded; I can't do much about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deal of the day: Do what you want, don't do what you don't want. Amen.&lt;/p&gt;
</content></entry><entry><title>29/05/2024 22:34 (Rats in weel)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/29052024-2234-rats-in-weel/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-05-29T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:4af4bdd7-460a-399f-8607-b29223df5f4e</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/the_abandoned_android_by_serendigity_art_dgjt3ct-pre.jpg'&gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;The Abandoned Android&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/serendigity-art/art/The-Abandoned-Android-1000728893" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by Serendigity-Art&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a gritty, neon-lit corner of Kingston, a lone hero emerged amidst the sprawling slums. Armed with nothing but discarded tech and an unwavering resolve, he assembled computers from spare parts and shared his knowledge with the children of the forgotten. In makeshift classrooms, he taught them to navigate the digital realm, to code their way out of poverty, and to sculpt their dreams in 3D.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was 2019, a time when the IT labor market was a searing crucible of opportunity, and those who could bend computers to their will were the new gods. But now, as I type these words onto a flickering screen, the world has shifted. The once-privileged class of computer specialists has been reduced to mere cogs in the machine, their value no greater than that of an office drone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The industry became a bloated beast, luring in the masses with promises of quick riches. They came in droves, hastily absorbing scraps of knowledge, only to turn on their own kind with sneers of superiority. It's a sickening sight, watching them cannibalize each other while the corporate overlords watch with glee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I digress. Those children in the computer club, they were supposed to be the future, their skills a shining path out of the darkness. Yet, as time has shown, perhaps they would have been better off learning the ancient arts of leatherwork or tending to the earth. For now, the gates to the hallowed halls of IT have slammed shut, and only those who entered before the great culling remain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the harsh reality, a truth I know all too well. The once-free spirits of the programming world have been reduced to lab rats, endlessly running on a wheel, their eyes fixed on the next morsel that falls from the dispenser. It's a bleak picture, I know, but the signs were there for those who cared to look. Copeland saw it, all those years ago in "Generation X," and now we're living it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just today, I met with the apartment administrator, a man who sought my aid in fixing his computer. When I asked for a meager tablet in return, he spouted some nonsense about everyone helping each other without expectation. I laughed silently and walked away, knowing all too well that in this world, nothing comes for free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;


&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: SHIKIMO -  Test Subject&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/SHIKIMO - Test Subject.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>28/05/2024 18:47 (Flatlined)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/28052024-1847-flatlined/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-05-28T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:837c5047-6941-3a8d-b99a-2ac3303f06e0</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container "&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/boxing.png'&gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Cyberpunk 2077&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="#" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by rst_lnlss&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I jack into the matrix and ping my Mom. In my parents' pad where I hosted last time, I still have my single-board rig and a souped-up wi-fi antenna. I need it, not sure why yet, but ideas spark when the gear's in front of me. I tell her to point the smartphone's eye at the table and mark where everything is. The package is en route, got a tracking number. Now, I wait.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, I hit up the proxy store to check on my order. leather bags canceled it, jacked up the price, and wanted me to confirm again. I rang them up and demanded a refund. Terrible service, but I've got a backup plan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To keep my endorphins flowing, I hit the boxing gym on my lunch break. Showed up, but they sent us packing. I'll try again tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What's the big deal today? Silence. I'm talking about the deafening silence and isolation in this society. Feels like everyone's flatlined, but I know they're still kicking. They just can't jack into the net.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;


&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Lights - Archive&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Archive - Lights [Full Version].mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>27/05/2024 00:50 (Bloody hell mail)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/27052024-0050-bloody-hell-mail/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-05-27T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:975e8ecf-30fd-3966-a524-850e87ff4916</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/trainer.jpg' class=leftimg&gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;AI generated&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="#" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by rst_lnlss&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh, endless Monday. Usually, I dig my gig, but not today. Today, I think my job mates left half their wetware at home. Fine, I set up smart alerts for this bloody hell mail client. To reduce the loneliness, I posted on a collective blog, but I can't stand the stupid and idle chatter. They don't need to know what I know, but... hell, they're just a mindless crowd, and I despise crowds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Affirmation: You don't have to feel bad in this neon-drenched society. Society isn't the Arctic cold from which only a warm parka can save you. Society and interactions are what fire up your neural circuits. I imagined myself as a sleek machine made of high-tech, shiny aluminum and chrome - nothing else could touch me. It seems to help; I'll have to try it again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Half the day, Darksynth wave blasted through my audials on rekt.network. Good, good. I've heard almost all of it. My brain craves it.
When I went to get a hit of caffeine from the machine, I saw my trainer. He walked towards me but didn't notice me. Remembering his lightning-fast and polished moves, I gave him a respectful nod and promised to jack in tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like rgb-flame from my mouse in dark kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Hugo Kant - Far From Home (Full Album)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;iframe width="300" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-tOSh9bDh00" title="Hugo Kant - Far From Home (Full Album)" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>26/05/2024 21:35 (Headphones and Arab philosophy)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/26052024-2135-headphones-and-arab-philosophy/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-05-26T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:0092fed2-0f86-3b09-9bed-f44abc8edf1f</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='/static/abu_size.png'&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey yo, I say to cyberspace and to myself. I decided to get out of my hole and walk the streets.   The goal is to find a place under the shimmering sky where you can connect to the matrix and immerse yourself in the code. As the old hacker taught me - be prepared for anything, especially the worst.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After packing my electronic arsenal into my bag, I downloaded a holographic map of the city onto my smartphone. The ghost bus, invisible to the system, was perfect for my quest. I jumped inside, plunging into the unknown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Retro headphones connected by wires to the head are my homage to the old school and a way to save energy in this cutthroat cyberpunk world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As soon as I had time to take a sip of my favorite sugar-free flat white, my smartphone vibrated, transmitting a message from the virtual world. A friend asks to connect a neural network to design a festival site in augmented reality. He promised to help, but the carefree mood evaporated like smoke from a cigarette. Phantom creds loomed on the horizon again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twice I walked past the open terraces of summer cafes, where for a cup of coffee you can buy a ticket to the eternity of cyberspace. Mission Complete. I moved to the air taxi call point, looking into an inconspicuous basement theater along the way. The poster promised a performance based on the biography of the legendary Arab anarchist philosopher Abu al-Ala al-Ma'arri. Alas, in an unfamiliar dialect, but I made it clear to the artistic director that I was following events and was ready to immerse myself in art.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Towards the end of the day, rekt.network brought out live Vosto, perfectly fitting into the mosaic of my cyberpunk existence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
Sound: &lt;b&gt;Death Internet Theory - Internet Death Machine&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content></entry><entry><title>26/05/2024 13:30 (Nutrients and smart bomb)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/26052024-1330-nutrients-and-smart-bomb/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-05-26T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:83a6f115-d928-3b3e-9326-f5e8f600381f</id><content type="html">&lt;div class="image-container leftimg"&gt;
&lt;img src='/static/techno_cube_vj_loop_by_riotstarter1988_devart.gif' class=leftimg &gt;
  &lt;div class="overlay"&gt;
    &lt;p class="title"&gt;Techno Cube VJ Loop&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://www.deviantart.com/riotstarter1988/art/Techno-Cube-VJ-Loop-836691405" target="_blank" class="artist"&gt;by Riotstarter1988&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morning ladies and gentlemen. I was build blog on static pages until 5 am, my fingers hovering over the keyboard, and the documentation lines helpfully indicated what to do, almost instantly. Everything worked out and I went into the capsule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For breakfast, I have planned a nutritious cocktail of cottage cheese, nuts and other nutritious things, the composition for which was selected for me by the AI. And while I was going to the store for natural milk, vague fragments of a dream about a technological singularity were still spinning in my head. I wanted to note this in my cloud notepad for the next blog entry and... I discovered that the notes on the smartphone are not synchronized. After digging through the logs, I checked several hypotheses, searched the bug tracker, didn’t find a solution, and swiped the data to download it from the cloud again. Sometimes it's easier to turn it off and on, really.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the background was the thought of a crazy dictator dropping a smart bomb on a construction hypermarket. Connecting to media gives us a feeling of belonging to the world and to reality, but to hell with this reality, I turn on the music. However, I am sure the thought remained in the subconscious and I do not avoid it, it makes me modern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Sound: Daft Punk &amp; Pharrell Williams - Lose Youself to Dance (Drumless Edition)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;
&lt;audio controls&gt;
  &lt;source src="/static/sound/Daft Punk - Lose Yourself to Dance (Drumless Edition) (Audio) ft. Pharrell Williams.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
  Your browser does not support the audio element.
&lt;/audio&gt;&lt;/td&gt; 
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>25/05/2024 22:48 (Backup coffee machine)</title><link href="http://resist-loneliness.blooddrop.live/blog/first-post/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2024-05-25T00:00:00Z</updated><author><name>rst_lnlss</name></author><id>urn:uuid:805645e6-3a97-3bdf-a407-64335bea570a</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src='/static/coffee_machine.jpg' class=leftimg&gt;
So, here's the log entry. Armenia, post-mobilization reality. The meat attacks didn't break me, I'm still in the game. Semi-legal cash flow from a remote location, a trusty laptop with access to the office network and the ability to get electronics - these are my arsenal.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Thoughts, dark and light, swarm in my head. I don’t suppress them, let consciousness grow freely. One of these thoughts is scam. Thousands of fake online stores, money for non-existent goods. But a moral compass does not allow you to go astray.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The light side took over. I created several websites for local shopkeepers, put on a formal biker jacket, and went to convince. But the Armenian infosphere is a separate universe, under the wing of Meta. Backup options? Did not hear. Thousands of years of history are probably to blame.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Today: the coffee machine at the supermarket malfunctioned just as I was rushing to a Lethal Company co-op session with two guys from the net. The money was returned, but the coffee had to be taken in backup.
The gaming session is fire. The work phone was silent, two hours of pure fun with the guys.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The dual boot laptop is buggy. Three freezes in Windows, once dead. I suspect the memory bar, but haven't gotten around to checking it yet.
rekt.network continues to provide excellent soundtracks. A couple more energy drinks and I'm back in business. The contours of a new project loom on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
Sound: &lt;b&gt;Abominable Beat Machine -  Dessicator&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content></entry></feed>